Little Junior Brown. He rules the streets. He owns the
game. But he doesn't own all of the players.
Kiss of Death is a crime, thriller, drama film directed by Barbet Schroeder.
Jimmy Kilmartin's an ex-con who's trying to go straight.
But he can't say no to a quick driving job because his
so-called friend's life is threatened.
The job is for Little Junior Brown, a violent and powerful villain.
When things go wrong, Jimmy is left to do the time, and his whole life is turned upside-down,
but if that wasn't enough, the cops won't leave Jimmy alone when he gets out...
They want Little Junior Brown.
Jimmy Kilmartin, played by David Caruso.
Little Junior Brown, played by Nicolas Cage.
Calvin Hart, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Bev Kilmartin, played by Helen Hunt.
Rosie Kilmartin, played by Kathryn Erbe.
Frank Zioli, played by Stanley Tucci.
Kiss of Death is a 1995 American crime thriller film directed and produced
by Barbet Schroeder, and starring David Caruso, Samuel L.
Jackson, Nicolas Cage, Helen Hunt, Ving Rhames and Stanley Tucci.
The film is a remake of the 1947 film noir classic of the same name that
starred Victor Mature, Brian Donlevy, and Richard Widmark.
It was screened out of competition at the 1995 Cannes Film Festival.
Like the original Kiss of Death, the film was released by 20th Century Fox.
The film explores themes of prison, new york city,
undercover agent, gangster, psychopath.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.